https://dev-dioceseofbrooklyn.pantheonsite.io/privacy-policy/

This site uses cookies to store information on your computer. By using this site, you consent to the placement and use of these cookies. Read our Privacy Policy to learn more.
ACCEPT
Updated May 1, 2018.
1. OUR COMMITMENT
Diocese of Brooklyn understands how important the protection of your personal information is to you. We are committed to protecting your privacy. To the extent this website is governed by its rules, we intend to fully comply with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
We want to make sure that you understand how the personal information you provide to us is being used as well as the choices that you have regarding this information.  The following policy discloses our procedures surrounding this commitment.
2. SCOPE OF POLICY
This Privacy Policy governs the privacy practices used by Diocese of Brooklyn on its web site (dioceseofbrooklyn.org). Diocese of Brooklyn maintains high standards for the protection and privacy of users of their Sites as well as for those that have offline interactions with Diocese of Brooklyn. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it states how we may collect, use, and disclose personal information about you. Please also read the Terms and Conditions governing your use of the Site.
The Site may contain links to web sites not under the Organizations’ control and managed by third parties with independent information and privacy practices. We strive to protect your information and suggest you read the privacy policies of the site to which you are redirected before supplying any personal information. In addition, we may have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. Accordingly, you should consult these other web sites’ privacy policies when accessing or using such other web pages.
3. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
Diocese of Brooklyn may gather some personal identifiable information from you when it is voluntarily submitted by you. The types of information collected may include but are not limited to your name, email address, phone number, credit card number and billing address, and residential and business postal addresses.
Diocese of Brooklyn collects information online in the following ways:
Upon registration as a user on our Web sites
Upon registration for a class or training session
From award nominations
Upon completion of our online forms and applications
Upon completion of our online surveys
Through email communications, including communications you originate from the “Contact Us” page
Upon your generous online donations
When updating personal information in your profile.
Automatic Collection: In the course of providing you with the services you find on our Site, our web and application server will automatically collect usage-related information, including the URLs that you access through our Site, the date and time of your usage, your Internet protocol (IP) address, your Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, number of clicks, and your browser type. We collect this information so we can perform effective capacity planning, administer the Site, troubleshoot Web site performance, track users’ movements in the aggregate, gather demographic information for aggregate use, and accurately document revenue-generating transactions from your generous online donations. We use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement in our site.
4. USE OF INFORMATION
All personally identifiable information obtained from you is treated with great care to protect your privacy and security. Except as discussed in Section 5, management authorizes only trained and qualified employees, agents performing duties on behalf of Diocese of Brooklyn, and contractors to access the information you choose to provide. Your personal information may be used to:
Build quality and useful services by analyzing user trends and by measuring demographics and interests
Communicate with you about your account or the Site
Communicate member violations and sanctions
Pre-populate online forms for your convenience
Provide you with prompt and effective service
Send you newsletters
Support the operation of the Site (for example: account maintenance, and troubleshooting such as access for the user).
Your personal information may also be used in other ways that you either imply or expressly give consent to or instruct us to undertake. We do not sell email addresses to any third party.
5. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
It is our commitment that your personal information is disclosed only to third parties to the extent needed to deliver a service or program in compliance with Diocese of Brooklyn. Vendors and third parties are prohibited from using this information for any purpose outside of the scope of the prescribed activities. Third parties with whom we may share selected personal information include but are not limited to:
Affinity partners
Google Analytics
Google AdWords
MailChimp
Our auditors
Conference attendees (for the conference you are registered for)
Mailing and fulfillment houses
Other participants when it is an inherent function of the Site you use, such as posting to a discussion area where your email address automatically appears or as permitted under the privacy policy, terms and conditions of the site
Such other third parties as permitted or required by law.
6. REVOCATION OF CONSENT
To the extent that you choose to revoke your consent for Diocese of Brooklyn to utilize cookies, all you need to do is let us know by clicking the “REVOKE CONSENT” button at the end of this Privacy Policy.  This button will redirect you to a third-party website outside of the Site.  If you return to the Site voluntarily, you may again be asked to provide your informed consent.
7. DATA BREACHES
In the event that Diocese of Brooklyn becomes actually aware of a personal data breach, Diocese of Brooklyn will timely notify the supervisory governmental authorities, unless the personal data breach is unlikely to result in a risk to the rights and freedoms of natural persons.  Diocese of Brooklyn may also choose to communicate high-risk breaches to affected data subjects, to the extent practicable.  To the extent you become aware of a possible data breach, please contact the Data Protection Officer.
8. DATA PROTECTION OFFICER
Diocese of Brooklyn’s current Data Protection Officer is Fidel Sciortino. He can be contacted by electronic mail at: privacy@desalesmedia.org.
Remove My Information
×
Join our email alert list to stay up-to-date on important news & events in our Diocese
Email
Zip Code
I'm aware that my information is being collected for marketing purposes. More info
Keep Me Informed
No Thanks
Join our email alert list to stay up-to-date important news & events in our Diocese
I'm aware that my information is being collected for marketing purposes. More info
Keep Me Informed
No Thanks
